bolalist.com 2017-12-15

# BolaList Privacy Policy

Bolalist USA Business Directory is sensitive to the privacy issues and we are committed to protecting your privacy in a manner that will allow you to use our resources with complete confidence and comfort. 

Only when voluntarily offered, Bolalist collects information that can identify you and uses this information in accordance with its privacy policy. When you sign up for our services Bolalist requests personal information and business information, including your business name,description of your pruducts and service name,Your name, e-mail address, and other information necessary to provide you with personalized service. 

Bolalist takes care to respect the privacy of its online visitors guests or members. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. At Bolalist we continuously strive to improve your experience. To do so, we internally use personally identifiable information to personalize the customer experience and to improve our content and product offering, and site design and layout. 

We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. We may share non-personal, aggregate information regarding customer demographics, traffic patterns, sales, and site usage with our partners or advertisers. We will never willfully disclose personally identifiable information about our customers to any third party without prior consent. 

We do not share personal information provided by site visitors with anyone outside Bolalist, except to the extent necessary to allow you to participate in site activities. In particular, we do not rent or sell mailing lists of site visitors to any third party. We will never post your e-mail address or other identifying information you have provided on our site without your consent. We collect non-personal information from online visitors in order to constantly improve our web site. 

Information that can identify a visitor (e.g. name or address) is not collected in this process, nor does Bolalist require disclosure of such information. Information that can identify a visitor is collected only when the visitor provides it voluntarily. 

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

We use advertising companies, third-party ads to show you, when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including name, address, email address or your phone number) about your visits to this site and other sites in order to provide advertisements for products and services of interest you.

If you want additional information regarding this process, and if you want to know how can I avoid these companies use this information, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx).

Google as Third-party retailer, uses cookie files to display ads in our site. Assistance in the use of a cookie file DART, Google can display ads based on users visit their sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may cancel your use of the file of the DART cookie by visiting the privacy policy of the ad and content network of Google [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Contacting Us:

If you have any questions about our site, this privacy policy, or our general procedures, please email us. 

[Click here](http://www.bolalist.com/addbiz.php) to add a business. After approval by our site's admin, your business will appear on our directory.
